Scott Ha

Tustin, California, United States

ha_scott@yahoo.com

7143529225

linkedin.com/in/hascottn

Summary

Experienced Full-stack Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in JavaScript, React.JS, Redux.JS, Ruby, Python, and SQL. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from California State University-Fullerton.

Experience

Noiz Software Engineer

Noiz

May 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

- Designed and Implemented Modular Components for new features using React.js
- Designed and Implemented API for new features using SAILS to reduce Monolithic Constraints

Noiz Junior Software Engineer

Noiz

Jul 2020 - May 2021 (11 months)

- Designed and Deployed a Microservice for the Main App using SAILS hosted on Droplet and Utilizes Amazon S3
- Ownership of Code Base and reviewing Merge Requests on GitLab

Noiz Software Engineer Intern

Noiz

May 2020 - Jun 2020 (2 months)

- Implemented UX Design Elements using HTML/SCSS
- Addressed Tickets Regarding SAILS API

Head Of Information Technology

ATI Electrical Supply

Feb 2018 - Oct 2019 (1 year 9 months)

- Lead the technical aspect of migrating the company's ERP to NetSuite and educated employees on the utilization of the new ERP
- Advised and implemented technological solutions for employees, both in-house and remote
- Organized and restructured processes for more efficient and productive environments for the employees

Junior Software Engineer

MCLSS

Dec 2016 - Jun 2017 (7 months)

- Interacted with customers directly and applied immediate solutions through the application software

- Designed and implement features to expand upon existing software
- Utilized SVN to commit and collaborate with team members that worked remotely

Education

App Academy

Full Stack Engineering (Ruby on Rails, MERN) 2019 - 2020

California State University, Fullerton

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2013 - 2016

Orange Coast College

Transfer, Undecided 2011 - 2013

Licenses & Certifications

- in Building a Personal Portfolio with Django LinkedIn
- in Learning npm the Node Package Manager LinkedIn

Skills

Sails.js • SCSS • JavaScript • React.js • MongoDB • Amazon S3 • HTML